{"data":[{"question":"The price _________, but I doubt whether it will remain so.","a":"will down","b":"went down","c":"was going down","d":"has gone down","answer":"4","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Hey, look where you are going! \"Oh, I'm terribly sorry. ___\"","a":"I didn't notice you","b":"I'm not noticing","c":"I don't notice","d":"I haven't notice","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Ben, you've left the light on. \"Oh, so I have. ___ and turn it off.\"","a":"I've gone","b":"I'll go","c":"I'm going","d":"I go","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the future simple to decide to do something at the time of speaking","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"How are you today, Henry? \"Oh, I _________ as bad as I do now for a very long time.\"","a":"wasn't feeling","b":"didn't feel","c":"haven't felt","d":"don't feel","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the present perfect tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The witness said that the UFO ___ north to south when she saw it.","a":"traveled","b":"was traveling","c":"was to travel","d":"had been traveling","answer":"2","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"I first met Lisa two years ago. She _________ at a bookstore at the time.","a":"was working","b":"had worked","c":"had worked","d":"had been working","answer":"1","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Is this coat yours? \"No, mine ___ there by the door.","a":"has hung","b":"hangs","c":"hung","d":"is hanging","answer":"4","explain":"- We use the present continuous","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Nancy is not waiting for us. But she ___!","a":"promised","b":"promises","c":"had promised","d":"will promise","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the past simple tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Shirley ___ a book about Russia last year but I don't know whether she has finished it.","a":"wrote","b":"has written","c":"was writing","d":"had written","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the past continuous","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Hi, Tracy, you look tired \"I am tired. I ___ my house all day.\"","a":"had painted","b":"painted","c":"have painted","d":"have been painting","answer":"4","explain":"- We use the present perfect continuous tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}